Guide to the Stanford Historical Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- General Photographs, Series 1
  - Earthquake (1989)--Encina Hall (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Earthquake (1989)--Library--(1919) (Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Earthquake (1989)--Memorial Church (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Earthquake (1989)--Museum (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Earthquake (1989)--Student Housing (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Eating Clubs (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Eating Clubs--Breakers--Fol.1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Eating Clubs--Breakers--Fol.2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Education, School of--Building (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Education, School of--Faculty (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Education, School of--Secondary Teacher Education Program (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Electrical Engineering, Department of (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory (ERL) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Elementary Schools on Campus (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Encina Wheelman (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Engineering--Alumni Groups (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Engineering--Faculty (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Engineering--Faculty--Books (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Engineering--Faculty/student groups--Fol.1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Engineering--Faculty/student groups--Fol.2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Engineering--Faculty/student groups--Fol.3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Exterior--Fol.1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Exterior--Fol.2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Interior--Fol.3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Interior--Fol.4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Engineering Laboratories--Interior--Fol.5 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Engineering--Students--Fol.1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Engineering--Students--Fol.2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Club--Buildings (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Faculty--Groups--Fol.1--(First Family, 1892) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Faculty--Groups--Fol.2--(Taken, Feb. 4, 1896) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Faculty--Groups--Fol.3 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Faculty--Groups--Informal (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Housing--Fol.1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Housing--Fol.2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Housing--Fol. 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Housing--Aerial Views (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Housing--Alvarado Road--Fol.1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Housing--Alvarado Road--Fol.2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Housing--Frenchman's Hill (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Housing--Pearce Mitchell--Dedication (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Housing--San Juan Hill (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Offices (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Felt Lake (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 50th Anniversary--June Events #1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 50th Anniversary--June Events #2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 50th Anniversary--June Events #3 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - 50th Anniversary--October Events (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fire Department (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Flying Club (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Founding Grant (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Free Campus Movement (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up--Fol.1 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up--Fol.2 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up--Fol.3 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up--Fol.4 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up--Fol.5 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Frost Amphitheater--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Geology Department--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Geology Department--Fol.2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Glee Club--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Glee Club--Fol.2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business--Conferences and Special Programs (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Griffins (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Guest Speaker and Lecturers (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Guggenheim Aeronautic Laboratory (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Gymnasium--Men--(1906) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Hacienda--Exteriors--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Hacienda--Interiors--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Hammer and Coffin (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Health Service, Student (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - High Energy Physics Laboratory (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - History Department (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Honeycomb House (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Hoover House, Lou Henry--Fol.1 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hoover House, Lou Henry--Fol.2 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hoover House, Lou Henry--Fol.3 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Hoover House, Lou Henry--Dedication as Historical Landmark (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hoover Institution (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Tower--Fol.1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Tower--Fol.2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station--Fol.1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station--Fol.2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Hopkins Marine Station--Fol.3 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Hopkins Marine Station--Fol.4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Hopkins Marine Station--Fol.5 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Interfraternity Council (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Japan, Stanford Alumni Assoc. of (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Japanese Students Association--Fol.1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Japanese Students Association--Fol.2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Japanese Students Association--Fol.3 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Jasper Ridge (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Jordan Club (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.1 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.2 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.5 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.6 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, David Starr-- Days of a Man--Misc. Photos--Fol.7 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Residences--Fol.1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, David Starr--Residences--Fol.2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Jordan Hall (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Jordan Quad (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Keystone, Laying of (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Kingscote Gardens (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Kings Mountain House (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Klystron (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Knoll (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - La Peire and Sons Grocery (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Laboratories--Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lake Lagunita--Fol.1 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lake Lagunita--Fol.2 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lake Lagunita--Fol.3 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Lake Lagunita--Boathouse--Fol.1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Lake Lagunita--Boathouse--Fol.2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Land Development (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Lasuen Street (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Law School (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Libraries--Art (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Libraries--Business School (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Libraries--Earth Sciences (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Libraries--Falconer Biology (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Libraries--Lane Medical Library (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Libraries--Law (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Libraries--Mathematics (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Dedication Ceremonies--Fol.1 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Dedication Ceremonies--Fol.2 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Dedication Ceremonies--Fol.3 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Dedication Ceremonies--Fol.4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Exteriors (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Libraries--Meyer--Interiors (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Libraries--Music (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Library, First--(1891)--(Building 10) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Library--(1900)--Cornerstone (Thomas Welton Stanford Library) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Library--(1900)--Interiors (Thomas Welton Stanford Library) (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Library (1906) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Library--(1919)--Exteriors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Library--(1919)--Exteriors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Library--(1919)--Exteriors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Library--(1919)--Exteriors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Library--(1919)--Floor Plans--(Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.3 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--(Cecil H. Green Library)--Fol.4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Bender Room--(Cecil H. Green Library)--(Pre-1982) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Felton Room--(Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Field Room--(Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Government Documents Room--(Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Hopkins Room (Rm.311)--(Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Library--(1919)--Interiors--Lurie Rotunda (Cecil H. Green Library) (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Library--(1980)--Exterior (Cecil H. Green Library, West Wing) (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Library Staff--Fol.1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Library Staff--Fol.2 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Library Staff--Fol.3 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Library Staff--Fol.4 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Library Staff--Fol.5 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Library Staff--Groups (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Library Staff--Picnics (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Madrono Hall--Fol.1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Madrono Hall--Fol.2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Mandolin Club (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Manzanita Hall (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Mariposa House (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Martin, Dennis--Church (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Dennis--Property (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mausoleum--Fol.1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Mausoleum--Fol.2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Mausoleum--Fol.3 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - MECHA (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Mechanical Engineering Laboratory (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center--Fol.1 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center--Fol.2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center--Anatomy Building (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center Heart Transplant (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Medical Center--Planning (Architect's Model) (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Medical School--San Francisco--Pre-1959--Fol.1 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Medical School--San Francisco--Pre-1959--Fol.2 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Arch--Fol.1 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Memorial Arch--Fol.2 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Memorial Arch--Fol.3 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Memorial Church--Activities (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Church--Cornerstone Ceremony (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Memorial Church--Mosaics (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Memorial Church--Organ (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.5 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Fol.6 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.3 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.4 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.5 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.6 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Memorial Church--Pre-1906--Interior--Fol.7 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Exterior--Fol.1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Exterior--Fol.2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Exterior--Fol.3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Exterior--Fol.4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Interior--Fol.1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church--Post-1906--Interior--Fol.2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Church--Stained Glass Windows (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Church--Weddings (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Court--Fol.1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Court--Fol.2 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Court--Fol.3 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Hall--Fol.1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Hall--Fol.2 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Menlo Park (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Mining and Metallurgy--Dept. of (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Minority Groups (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell Earth Science Building (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Motion Picture Research (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Mudd, Seeley G. Chemistry Building (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Mudfight (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Museum Employees (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Original Building--Fol.1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Original Building--Fol.2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Original Building--Fol.3 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--Original Building--Fol.4 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--with Wing Additions--Fol.1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--with Wing Additions--Fol.2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--with Wing Additions--Fol.3 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Museum--Pre-1906--Exteriors--with Wing Additions--Fol.4 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Museum--Miscellaneous--Exteriors--(and/or date not established) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Museum--Post-1906--Exteriors (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Museum--Interiors--Fol.1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Museum--Interiors--Fol.2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Museum--Interiors--Fol.3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.1 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.2 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.3 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.4 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.5 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.6 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Fol.7 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Egyptian--Fol.1 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Egyptian--Fol.2 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Mrs. Stanford's Lace Collection (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Museum--Interiors--Exhibits--Statuary (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Music Department (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Musical Groups--Chorus (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Naval ROTC (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - News and Publications Service (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Nursery School--Bing (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Nursing, School of (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Oaks (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Opening Day Ceremonies (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Opening Day Ceremonies (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Opera in Stadium (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Orchestra--Fol.1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Orchestra--Fol.2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Organic Chemistry Building (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Oval, The (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Overseas Campuses (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Owen House (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Padre's Font (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Pajamarino (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Palm Drive--Fol.1 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Palm Drive--Fol.2 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Palm Drive--Fol.3 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Palm Drive--Entrance Gates--(Original Gates)--Fol.1 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Palm Drive--Entrance Gate--(Second Set of Gates--Destroyed in 1906 Earthquake)--Fol.2 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Palm Drive--Entrance Gates--(Second Set of Gates--Destroyed in 1906 Earthquake)--Fol.3 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Palm Drive--Entrance Gates--(Second Set of Gates--Destroyed in 1906 Earthquake)--Fol.4 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Palm Drive--Reconstruction (1994) (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Palo Alto--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Palo Alto--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Palo Alto--Fol.3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Palo Alto Airport--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto Airport--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto Film Corporation (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Palo Alto Railroad Station (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Single Trunk--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Single Trunk--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Single Trunk--Fol.3 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Single Trunk--Fol.4 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Single Trunk--Fol.5 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Tree--Twin Trunk (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Peninsular Railway Co.--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Peninsular Railway Co.--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Philippine Curriculum Library Project (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Physics Tank--Exterior (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Physics Tank--Interior (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Physiology Research Laboratory (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Plug Ugly--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Plug Ugly--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Police Department (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Post Office--Fol.1 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Post Office--Fol.2 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Power House--Exterior (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Power House--Interior (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - President's Office (bombing of) (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Press Club (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Psychology Department (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.6 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Quad--Arcades, Views Down--Fol.7 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Quad--Arches--Detail--Fol.1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Quad--Arches--Detail--Fol.2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Quad--Arches--Detail--Fol.3 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Quad--Engineering Corner (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Quad--Fences--Detail (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-Outer Quad--Fol.1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-Outer Quad--Fol.2 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.5 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Quad--Front Views--Pre-1906--Fol.6 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Quad--Front Views--Post-1906--Fol.1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Quad--Front Views--Post-1906--Fol.2 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Quad--Front Views--Post-1906--Fol.3 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Quad--Front Views--Post-1906--Fol.4 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Fol.1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Fol.2 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Fol.3 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Fol.4 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Close Shots (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Views through (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Quad--Gates--East and West--Views from Outside of Quad (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Quad--Geology Corner (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Quad--History Corner (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.2 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.3 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.4 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.5 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.6 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.7 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Pre-1906--Fol.8 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Quad--Inner Courtyard--Post-1906 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Quad--Inner--Landscaping (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Quad--Interior Views (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Quad--Lanterns on Front Steps (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Quad--Memorial Court Entrance--Fol.1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Quad--Memorial Court Entrance--Fol.2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Quad--Memorial Court Entrance--Fol.3 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Quad--Miscellaneous Views--Pre-1906--Fol.1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Quad--Miscellaneous Views--Pre-1906--Fol.2 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Quad--Miscellaneous Views--Post-1906 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Quad--Physics Corner (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Quad, Stanford (student yearbook) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Radio Club (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Radio Station KZSU (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Radio Telescope (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ram's Head (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Registrar's Office (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Registration--Fol.1 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Registration--Fol.2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Riding Stables and Paddocks (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Roble Bridge (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Roll of Honor (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Rooting Section--Fol.1 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Rooting Section--Fol.2 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Rooting Section--Big Game--Fol.1 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Rooting Section--Big Game--Fol.2 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Rooting Section--Big Game--Fol.3 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Rooting Section--Cheerleaders--Rally Committees (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - ROTC--Reserve Officers Training Corps (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Rough's Day (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Ryan High Voltage Lab--Fol.1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ryan High Voltage Lab--Fol.2 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Ryan High Voltage Lab--Fol.3 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Ryan High Voltage Lab--Fol.4 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Ryan High Voltage Lab--Fol.5 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - San Francisco Scenes (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - San Francisquito Creek (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Sand Hill Road (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Santa Cruz Portland Cement Co. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships--Donors and In Memory of--Fol.1 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships--Donors and In Memory of--Fol.2 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Scholarships--Donors and In Memory of--Fol.3 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Searsville Dam Construction [Xerox] (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Searsville Dam Construction (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Searsville Lake (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Sequoia, The (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Serra House (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sheep on campus (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Skull and Snakes (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Sleep Disorders Clinic (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Snow at Stanford (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Southern Pacific Depots (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Spanish American War (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Spring Ridge (Windy Hill--West Side--Portola Valley) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Staff-- Fol.1, 1970's-- (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Staff-- Fol.2, 1970's-- (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Ambulance Corps (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home--Fol.1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home--Fol.2 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home--Con Home Week (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Daily, The (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Historical Society--Fol.1 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Historical Society--Fol.2 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Historical Society--Fol.3 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Stanford in Germany (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Stanford in Italy (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Inn (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center--Fol.1 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center--Fol.2 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center--Fol.3 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center--Georges Pompidou Visit (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Research Institute--Fol.1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Research Institute--Fol.2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Research Institute--Fol.3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Research Institute--Fol.4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Union--Old Student Union--Fol.1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Union--Old Student Union--Fol.2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Union--Old Student Union--Fol.3 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Union--Old Student Union--Fol.4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Union--Old Student Union--Fol. 5 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Peak (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University, Seal of (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Statuary--"Faith" (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Stauffer Chemistry Buildings (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Steam Plant (Box 43, Folder 14)